my name is Fatima castle first all I
首先我叫法蒂玛城堡
want to tell you that I am Spanish on my
想告诉你我是西班牙人
English is not very good but why would i
英语不是很好，但是我为什么会
well I will try to speak in English as
好吧，我会尽量说英语
best I can
尽我所能
so my apologies for this I have been
所以我为此道歉
working in software development for
从事软件开发工作
eight years and currently I work as Java
八年了，目前我从事Java工作
architect and a scrum master in
架构师和Scrum主管
paradigmatic no logic a software company
范式无逻辑的软件公司
formerly seen seven years ago I am
我以前看过七年前
specialized in groovy and grails
专长于groovy和grails
technologies and recently I'm interested
技术，最近我很感兴趣
in promote projects finally I want to
最后我要推广项目
find two organizers for giving me the
找到两个组织者给我
opportunity of a stay here today well
今天在这里住的机会很好
insert what are we going to see in this
插入我们将在此看到的内容
talk first I have to tell you that this
先说说我要告诉你
is an introduction about a stream good
是关于流的介绍
I'm grooving so if you know all about
我正在开槽，所以如果您知道所有有关
both I think you can see anything new in
我都认为你可以看到任何新东西
this talk well as I have already said
就像我已经说过的那样
I'm going to talk about the spring mood
我要谈谈 Spring 的心情
and grooving and where you could use
和开槽以及可以在哪里使用
proving your stream boots project
证明您的流启动项目
because I think that usually when when
因为我认为通常什么时候
somebody talked about a spring would
有人谈论 Spring 会
think about Java as development language
考虑将Java作为开发语言
because they don't know Ruby or they
因为他们不了解Ruby或他们
don't know that that can use groovy in a
不知道那可以在
steamboat project but yes you can use
汽船项目，但是可以使用
groovy as language in a spring mood
时髦作为 Spring 心情中的语言
project even some component components
甚至投影一些组件
of a spring boat are implemented with
Spring 船的实现与
gluing so we go to see a short
粘合，所以我们去看一小段
introduction of a spring board a short
Spring 板的介绍很短
introduction of moving on how or where
介绍如何或在何处移动
use both together for example using
一起使用，例如使用
Gradle Gradle developing test with
Gradle Gradle开发测试
groovy on the spoke framework you
关于辐条框架的常规
template or why not anywhere in your
模板，或者为什么不在您的任何位置
single project also I will tell you how
一个项目，我也会告诉你
to use gone on years piece in a stream
在流中使用多年
would throw it outside graves and I will
会把它扔到坟墓外面，我会
show you many cold give you examples of
给你看很多感冒给你的例子
all I want to show in this talk in first
我想在本次演讲中展示的所有内容
place what is s promote it's primo
放置什么促进它的原始
disapproved from a spring not allow you
Spring 拒登不允许您
to develop a standalone and spring MVC
开发独立的 Spring MVC
applications easily probably using about
应用很容易使用
the many configurations there are in
有许多配置
extreme project but a Streamwood follows
极端项目，但随后有Streamwood
convention over configuration allowing
约定优于配置
Auto configuration or configuration with
自动配置或使用
annotations eliminating the necessity of
注释消除了
use XML configuration files in order
按顺序使用XML配置文件
home stream would allow you to start and
家庭流可以让您开始
build production application quickly
快速建立生产应用程序
because providing the embedded container
因为提供嵌入式容器
and database according to the
和数据库根据
dependencies is specified in the build
依赖关系在构建中指定
system so you don't need to configure
系统，因此您无需进行配置
this to start work originally we can use
本来可以开始使用的工作
brewing of course all of these futures
当然所有这些期货的酝酿
only including on dependency or other
仅包括依赖或其他
dependencies related with with it
与之相关的依赖
finally we can run an application on
最终我们可以在
quickly turns to promote CLI - of course
快速转向提升CLI-当然
you can find samples on documentation
您可以在文档中找到样本
about all of this on the Streamwood
关于Streamwood的所有这些
website now the other main actor in this
现在是网站的另一个主要演员
talk is growing you know grew is a
谈话在增长，你知道增长是一个
dynamic language optionally tied it with
动态语言可选地与
a static typing and static compilation
静态类型化和静态编译
capabilities capabilities for the Java
Java的功能
platform
平台
thanks to NEC an expressive syntax is
感谢NEC，表达语法是
easy to learn for Java developers
Java开发人员易于学习
furthermore it integrates easily with
此外，它易于集成
any Java program delivering powerful
任何提供强大功能的Java程序
filters including closure runtime and
过滤器，包括关闭运行时和
compile time meta programming functional
编译时元编程功能
programming is creating powerful test so
编程正在创建强大的测试，因此
on so if we combine the powerful of a
因此，如果我们结合了
stream built with the future of Rubik we
用Rubik的未来打造的流
obtain a couple of powerful tools that
获得一些强大的工具
allows to developers work in an easy on
允许开发人员轻松进行
more productive interesting and amazing
更有趣，更有趣
way let me let me to solve it with
让我让我解决的方式
samples first we're going to see a
首先采样，我们将看到
little but powerful example that we can
我们可以做的小而有力的例子
develop an application that can be
开发一个可以
contain it in a single tweet and execute
将其包含在一条推文中并执行
it quickly we're testing good CLI but
很快我们正在测试良好的CLI，但是
before this I want to talk about an
在此之前，我想谈一谈
useful useful tool could be you already
有用的有用工具可能是您已经
know this tool is Vivian did you know
知道这个工具是Vivian吗？
Vivian yes this is the group environment
Vivian是的，这是团体环境
manager tool is for manager managing
经理工具用于经理管理
version of multiple multiple software
多个软件版本
development kits such as Ruby graves
开发套件，例如Ruby Graves
radial stream but I will use use it some
径流，但我会用它
of these in in example to use it you can
在示例中使用它们，您可以
Dolan download in its website to be
Dolan在其网站上下载是
entered outlet it's running most unique
进入插座，它运行得最独特
system as Linux Mac Solaris or in
系统作为Linux Mac Solaris或
Windows we say win is written in bus and
我们说胜利的窗户是用公共汽车和
only depends of course and unzip
当然只取决于并解压缩
these are the actual candidates this we
这些是我们的实际候选人
grow we don't really really candidates I
成长，我们并不是真正的候选人
show you quickly how to install TVN on
快速向您展示如何在TVN上安装TVN
how to install install the latest
如何安装安装最新
version of a spring mode you can see in
您可以在其中看到的Spring 模式版本
this line first to install and on that
该线首先安装，并在
TVN tool and later some lines that you
TVN工具以及您之后的一些行
have to write in bus
必须在公共汽车上写
Persie fighting unique systems this is a
Persie与独特的系统作战，这是
list of useful commands of given tool
给定工具的有用命令列表
for example help to show how to use EVM
例如帮助说明如何使用EVM
to lease available versions install it
租赁可用版本安装
version on the Cuban version you are
版本是古巴版本
using install to specifying the will see
使用安装指定将看到
own of framework vm used to specify the
框架vm的所有者，用于指定
version of a framework that you want to
您想要的框架版本
use in this terminal UBN default to
在此终端中使用UBN默认为
specify the cooperation of a framework
指定框架的合作
that you want to use always or giving
您想一直使用或给予的
children to list all current versions of
孩子列出所有当前版本
all Springvale you have install it or
您已安装的所有Springvale或
respective on the framework uninstall
分别在框架上卸载
also to an installation of a framework
也要安装框架
and this is the code of the grooviest
这是最时髦的代码
clip that you can Brown these can be
剪辑，你可以布朗这些可以
contained in a in a treat
包含在零食中
here we have the we have some lines in
在这里，我们有一些行
Nottingham I have annotations at rest
诺丁汉，我在休息时有注解
controller that means this is a
控制器，这意味着这是一个
controller component northern
北部控制器组件
annotations to for example request map
注释，例如请求地图
into later mine the URI finally a simple
到后来我的URI终于一个简单的
method that returns the message
返回消息的方法
helloworld to execute this we open our
helloworld要执行此操作，我们打开我们的
terminal and
终端和
- this part that contains the groovy
-包含常规的部分
script type a spring from hello world
脚本键入来自Hello World的Spring
that blooming this execute we go to see
那花开的执行，我们去看看
okay
好的
okay this is my escape
好的，这是我的逃生
okay and I have
好，我有
install a some version of a spring boat
安装一些版本的Spring 船
so if I run in string hello world
所以如果我在字符串hello world中运行
please start the application start its
请启动应用程序启动其
application introduction
应用介绍
so if we go to local host 8080 sorry
所以如果我们去 localhost 8080对不起
you can see that this is easy cutie
你可以看到这很容易
but what happens behind behind this
但是背后发生了什么
these Nissa water scrip if you want run
这些Nissa水草，如果您想跑步
we see a little it's like this but
我们看到有点像这样，但是
really if we want to execute this groovy
真的，如果我们要执行此常规
excrete with grooving it must have these
开槽排泄它必须有这些
lines you know they'll harm the use of
您知道的线会损害使用
grape grape is our er dependency manager
葡萄是我们的依赖性经理
embedded into groovy let you quickly add
嵌入groovy让您快速添加
maven repository dependencies to your
Maven存储库对您的依赖
class path making a scripting even
类路径，甚至可以编写脚本
easier the simple fuse is as simple as
简单的保险丝就像
adding a notation of your script that as
为您的脚本添加一个符号
well
好
also I have to include some input and a
我还必须包括一些输入和一个
main method that you can see here so if
您可以在这里看到的主要方法
we go to execute
我们去执行
this is the script with great with the
这是与伟大的脚本
use of grade if I ask you this withdrew
如果我要求您撤回，请使用等级
it
它
these do the same and we do with
这些都一样，我们
experiencia like okay we go it's the
就像好吧，我们去了
same okay
一样好
now what could you use bruit in what
现在你能在什么中使用bruit
could you introduce glue in various
你能介绍各种胶水吗
remote applications in short in any way
简而言之，远程应用程序
okay but we go to see the different
好的，但是我们去看看不同的地方
sites in the pro yet where you could use
专业人士尚未使用的网站
groovy bit by bit the first option is
groovy点点滴滴的第一个选择是
your groovy in the process to build the
在构建过程中您的常规
project using Gradle with a spin boot we
使用带有旋转启动的Gradle的项目
can build our project with maven but
可以用Maven建立我们的项目，但是
also we can use credit which we can
我们也可以使用信用
integrate with maven we have to manage
与我们必须管理的Maven集成
static is ml 5 the phone dot XML file
静态是ml 5电话点XML文件
but with Gradle we have a flexible and
但是有了Gradle，我们可以灵活地
modular groovy file that is more easy to
模块化的groovy文件，更易于
read thanks to a friendly sintered base
阅读感谢友好的烧结基地
on groovy DSL and uploading model read
在Groovy DSL上并读取模型
with Gradle we have a powerful building
有了Gradle，我们拥有了一座强大的建筑
tool with any future many features such
具有未来许多功能的工具
as super formal deploy yet dependency
作为超级正式部署，但具有依赖性
management based on Apache ivy with
基于Apache Ivy的管理
super an integration with maven on Ivy
在Ivy上与Maven超级集成
repositories also we have a large list
仓库也有很多
of tasks based on ant to manage our
ant 管理我们的任务
application we go to see some code to
应用程序，我们去看一些代码
install Gradle and create spring boot
安装Gradle并创建Spring Boot
and we can download a manage our version
我们可以下载一个管理我们的版本
of weather with given to it later we
天气，后来我们
only need to create a built at Gradle
只需要在Gradle上创建一个build
file with some dependencies execute the
具有某些依赖性的文件执行
common radio bill to compile test on
通用无线电法案，用于汇编测试
assemble the code into agile file these
将这些代码汇编成敏捷文件
are these are some lines to to execute
这些是要执行的几行吗
example if we execute Gradle tests we
例如，如果我们执行Gradle测试，
can see a list of available for our
可以看到可供我们使用的列表
project
项目
this is an example of build a trailer to
这是制作预告片的示例
start to work with with a steamboat we
开始与汽船合作，我们
can see some plugins such as groovy idea
可以看到一些插件，例如groovy idea
or extreme boat also we have got the
还是极限船，我们也有
configurations about the year 5 they
关于5年级的配置
name on the version of our project below
在下面的项目版本中命名
the repository is configuration and the
存储库是配置，
dependencies if you include some
依赖性，如果您包括一些
plugging more and execute they test
插入更多并执行测试
common and you will continue tasks in
常见，您将继续执行任务
the list the tacks are related with the
大头钉与
dependencies available in there in the
那里可用的依赖项
project this is the the main application
项目这是主要的应用
class to start with spin boot in this
类从旋转启动开始
example only we have this the the main
仅示例，我们主要
method and the notation is printed
方法和符号被打印
application to start we go to a security
申请开始我们去了安全
sample
样品
we go and go to stop
我们去停下来
I create the one
我创建一个
we create their razor file and we create
我们创建他们的剃刀文件，然后创建
a new application line class
一个新的应用程序类
now if we run if we if we run great this
现在，如果我们运行，如果我们运行得很好，这
showed a list of terms of a label this
显示了此标签的术语列表
is this moment but if I edit been graded
这是现在，但是如果我编辑已评分
and copy the lines of the the
并复制
I execute the game
我执行游戏
I have a son
我有一个儿子
sometimes more for example related to
有时更多例如与
the ID plugin okay now I edit the
ID插件好了，现在我编辑
application that groovy file and put the
groovy文件并将其放入的应用程序
lines of the example
示例行
I'm not
我不是
come bite me
来咬我
oops
哎呀
so I'm fine no baby
所以我很好没有孩子
this is a cube Santa's finally been
这是一个立方体，圣诞老人终于
successful and now razor run and run
成功，现在剃刀运行
application
应用
yesterday application
昨天申请
and that application is is wrong okay
而且那个应用程序是错误的好吗
okay I go to continue with examples okay
好吧，我继续举例
the next aspect is testing with a Spock
下一个方面是使用Spock进行测试
do you know Spock answer framework to
你知道Spock的答案框架吗
test applications yes okay this is
测试应用程序，是的，这是
another site where you screwy he's
另一个网站，你搞砸了他
implementing testing using the framework
使用框架实施测试
Spock for me this is my favorite section
Spock对我来说是我最喜欢的部分
I like to implement s with Ruby and I
我喜欢用Ruby实现，
spoke framework I think that is very
发言框架，我认为这非常
easily on is funny okay I spoke it's not
轻松地上是有趣的，好吧，我说的不是
only a test framework and Spock is a
只是一个测试框架而Spock是一个
specification for groovy and Java
groovy和Java规范
projects with an expressive language
表达语言的项目
it's also base it on ruby dsls this
它也是基于ruby dsls的
makes our tests become easy to read and
使我们的测试变得易于阅读和
well-documented moreover when an
此外，当
assertion failed and the axis is very
断言失败并且轴非常
very intuitive and easy to read as well
非常直观，也易于阅读
we go to see some examples for example
我们去看一些例子
this is a test with a Spock that is the
这是Spock的测试
Google Maps API in this example we can
在此示例中，我们可以使用Google Maps API
see that we spoke we can define tests
看到我们说的可以定义测试
with descriptive signatures we can
带有描述性签名，我们可以
organize the code in intuitive blocks
以直观的方式组织代码
such as given or set up to set up
例如给定或设置
initial variables for example going to
初始变量例如
execute an action then to test the
执行一个动作然后测试
result in this block we need an we need
结果在这个块中，我们需要一个我们需要
a set only test if our sentence is true
仅在我们的句子为真的情况下进行测试
or not by the use of Ruby true
是否通过使用Ruby true
this is another example and in this in
这是另一个例子
this case we have to block small is
这种情况下，我们必须阻止小是
and we're with these blocks we can test
我们可以通过这些块进行测试
different combinations of data in only
仅在不同的数据组合
one test later we will see what
一个测试以后，我们将看到
iteration it has failed and what not
迭代失败了，没有
easily here we we can build the weights
在这里我们可以轻松建立权重
also the associate is very easily the
员工也很容易
failure
失败
in addition to this we have more
除此之外，我们还有更多
features with different tax and
具有不同税种的功能和
utilities you can visit the
您可以访问的实用程序
documentation on taste these samples and
这些样品的味道文档以及
I think that this is a good point to
我认为这是对
start with grooving know the futures and
从开槽开始，了解期货，
the simplicity of the language this is
语言的简单性是
an example of rapport with spoke okay in
言语融洽的例子
this case we can see the different
这种情况下我们可以看到不同
iteration of the of the air test and
空中测试的迭代和
what fail what failed and what not okay
什么失败什么失败什么不好
if you have to use spoke in operate with
如果您必须将辐条用于
a spring boot
spring boot
you must include these dependencies in
您必须在其中包含这些依赖项
the bit that parade l5 okay you want to
游行l5好一点，你想
see more information for example in
查看更多信息，例如
these in this side there are more
这些在这边还有更多
examples in these side dogs that a
这些边狗的例子
spring framework that all there is the
Spring Framework ，所有的一切
documentation of this the spring
今年 Spring 的文件
framework and now go to AC cube is
框架，现在转到AC多维数据集是
samples
样本
I have this project
我有这个项目
this is a simple explained steamboat
这是一个简单的解释汽船
project and we have the application main
项目，我们有应用程序主体
class they've been graded file with no
他们已经被分级的课程，没有
dependencies
依存关系
i implement i this aspect with facebook
我用facebook实现这方面
this is the example that i saw before
这是我以前看到的例子
okay and now I go to execute with
好吧，现在我去执行
education test this is the list of tags
教育测试，这是标签列表
of graded
的等级
okay
好的
we have their results
我们有他们的结果
the output of the execute execution okay
执行执行的输出好了
and we go to see the generated report
我们去看看生成的报告
this is the report and this is the
这是报告，这是
execution okay in this case in this test
在这种情况下，在这种情况下可以执行
we can't print
我们无法打印
the different values of the address
地址的不同值
variable thanks to the rock and roll
多变的摇滚
okay well we go to continue
好吧，我们继续
I said before we can use groovy anywhere
我说过在任何地方都可以使用groovy
in our stream both applications we can
在我们的流中，我们可以
use groovy in controllers so main
在控制器中使用常规
classes repositories services in any way
以任何方式对存储库服务进行分类
and if we need we can combine Java and
如果需要，可以将Java和
Ruby easily that is if we need have
Ruby很容易，那就是如果我们需要
classes in Java one reason and you know
Java中的类的一个原因，你知道
the classes in groovy it is possible
groovy中的类是可能的
okay and you must know that the most
好，你必须知道最
important features of obvious groovy
明显的槽纹的重要特征
over Java is that our application will
在Java上，我们的应用程序将
be very simple expressive and flexible
表现力非常简单和灵活
and will have less code and if there are
并会减少代码，如果有的话
less code there will be less error we we
更少的代码，更少的错误
are more productive furthermore we
而且生产力更高
groobie we we have many features
groobie我们有很多功能
available than with Jara because we
比Jara可用，因为我们
provide the GDK as a station of jdk with
将GDK作为jdk的站提供
many many features about the use of
关于使用的许多功能
string collections control structures
字符串集合控制结构
closures and so on
封闭等
finally and you could think about the
最后，您可以考虑一下
computation in run run time our dynamic
在运行时计算我们的动态
typing but if you are worried about this
打字，但是如果你担心这个
you must know that you can use a static
您必须知道可以使用静态
compilation or a static typing with
编译或静态键入
annotation at compile a static and side
注释在编译静态和边
check in in your classes in short all
简而言之，请全部上课
you think about
你在想
all you think about you can do with Java
您认为可以使用Java进行的所有操作
and you can do with groovy and and more
您可以使用groovy等等
now I am going to show you how to count
现在我将向您展示如何计算
interment arrays IPI with our main class
插入数组IPI与我们的主要班级
JP a repository I controller using a
JP我控制的存储库
string data race and a spring that JPA
字符串数据竞赛和JPA的 Spring
well this is a very simple example but
好吧，这是一个非常简单的例子，但是
you can complete our not much
你可以完成我们很多
functionality as you want this is an
您想要的功能是
example of other main class we explained
我们解释了其他主要类别的例子
at the Jaypee a simple customer class
在Jaypee进行简单的客户培训
with three three attributes emitted per
每个发出三个三个属性
string and here we have a repository
字符串，这里有一个存储库
class of spin data rates on a string
字符串上旋转数据速率的类别
data GPA I use the data annotation
数据GPA我使用数据注释
repository dress research and I define
仓库着装研究，我定义
the relation on the path to access to
访问路径上的关系
the today to the customers and only here
今天的客户，只有这里
I I implemented method find my last name
二实施方法找我的姓
okay
好的
later this is the example of our
后来这是我们的例子
customer controller we with only method
客户控制器我们唯一的方法
fun by ID but otherwise the methods that
通过ID有趣，但其他方法
provide the repository in the
在以下位置提供存储库
application that groovy in application
groovy在应用中的应用
class I put some lines to add some some
课上我加了几行
customers at the titleist then append NC
标题专家的客户然后附加NC
is that you need to start to work with
是你需要开始与
example is our RVs extrema to start a
例如我们的房车极值开始
database on a Streamwood started by the
由
GPA for example a8 to database in this
GPA例如a8到数据库
site you can find more more examples and
您可以在该网站上找到更多示例，
documentation about this example
有关此示例的文档
I go to execute example
我去执行例子
we can see the customer domain class the
我们可以看到客户域类
customer controller the customer
客户控制者客户
repository and also I have added some
存储库，我也添加了一些
tests the customers I suspect
测试我怀疑的客户
today's the the IP I dress okay create a
今天的IP我穿好了，创建一个
new customer via race and final customer
通过种族和最终客户吸引新客户
via rest and also the customer respect
通过休息以及客户的尊重
to this repository
到这个仓库
okay with expect and work blocks now I
现在可以期待和工作了
go to execute some best of gravy
去执行一些最好的肉汁
Oh
哦
okay
好的
if I go
如果我走
what happened
发生了什么
one
一
sorry ain't going to see what happened
抱歉，不会看到发生了什么
customer
顾客
Oh
哦
sorry I don't know why these not work
对不起，我不知道为什么这些都不起作用
yes but in the customer repository I
是的，但是在客户存储库中
have the bad customer I try at least I
至少我有不好的顾客
don't know
不知道
you know I try to clean and work again
你知道我尝试再次清洁和工作
sorry
抱歉
is that you think though
是你认为
okay
好的
please
请
run
跑
okay
好的
thanks without the name of application
谢谢，没有申请的名字
sides on yes
双方是
I
一世
no I'm not no yes I don't I can see
不，我不是，不是，我看不到
sorry
抱歉
I I try with with from lighter note what
我尝试用打火机注意什么
happens this is a day Jason with the
碰巧这是Jason与
customers and also I can say like 119 or
客户，我也可以说119或
find my last name
找到我的姓
okay
好的
well this is the sample of IP I dressed
好吧，这是我穿着的IP的样本
with Ruby I continued with Ruby 10
使用Ruby我继续使用Ruby 10
plates
盘子
another possibility is the use of groovy
另一种可能性是使用groovy
templates glue a template framework is
模板胶是一个模板框架
based on markup guild build that permits
基于允许的标记公会构建
a pretty and easy way to write with a
一种漂亮而简单的书写方式
value reviews using Ruby DSL I also
使用Ruby DSL进行价值评估
provide an easy way to replace variables
提供替换变量的简便方法
in the view you can use slide out in
在视图中，您可以使用滑出
Ruby 10 places we go to so in the next
我们接下来要去的Ruby 10个地方
example I go to show you how to use
我去告诉你如何使用的例子
groovy templates and then a new method
常规模板，然后是一种新方法
in our controller a new controller to
在我们的控制器中，有一个新控制器
render a home page this is a template
渲染主页，这是一个模板
for lease customer and we have fun you
出租客户，我们很开心
will block where our customer list is
将阻止我们的客户列表在哪里
iterated and for each one its name is
重复，每个名字都叫
printed in Li element and as you can see
如您所见，以Li元素印制
we can pass a lease of lease and
我们可以通过租赁契约
iterated in in the individually if we
如果我们逐个迭代
return this v1 in the model we send this
在模型中返回此v1，我们将其发送给
leaf of customers we obtain the result
客户叶我们得到结果
we go to see running application ok to
我们去看看正在运行的应用程序可以
use this you need to add this dependency
使用这个你需要添加这个依赖
in they will integral that will fight ok
他们将积分，将战斗确定
stimulus that will be template and in
刺激将是模板
these sites you can see more more
这些网站，您可以看到更多
examples of the use of the template I go
我去使用模板的例子
to execute
执行
I love this top application
我喜欢这个顶级应用
we have a new home controller that
我们有一个新的家庭控制器
rainless the class model of you and I
你和我的课堂模型
pass then in the path of the view and
然后在视图的路径中通过
some variables okay
一些变量好吗
the view is here in resources then plate
视图在这里资源然后板
views from template this is the template
来自模板的视图，这是模板
also we apply a layout this is the
我们也应用布局这是
layout okay as you can see it's very
布局还可以，因为您可以看到它非常
simple define some components on
简单定义一些组件
elements of an html5 in this example I
在此示例中，html5的元素
pass
通过
somebody able money in this way okay
有人可以用这种方式赚钱好吗
this way
这条路
the other method in the customer control
客户控制中的另一种方法
it is to these customers I written this
是我写给这些客户的
model of you and I pass the path of the
你我的榜样，我走过了
view of the template and I pass the list
模板的视图，我通过列表
of all customers this is the template as
在所有客户中，这是模板
you can see me some fun okay
你可以看到我一些有趣的东西
you may vote
你可以投票
customers
顾客
this is the template okay I print a list
这是模板好吧，我打印列表
of customer and it is a simple link to
客户，这是一个简单的链接
go home the home controller okay it's
回家的家庭控制器好吧，这是
very simple only so the use of groovy
很简单，所以使用groovy
templates okay the next aspect is the
模板好，下一个方面是
use of Gore gonna miss the claims of yet
戈尔的使用会错过
relational mapping for our grades and
我们的年级和
since drains the to that for it's
因为它耗尽了它的
possible to use gone outside of race and
可以使用种族以外的东西
these permits access relational database
这些允许访问关系数据库
or MongoDB with Gore in for example a
或带有Gore的MongoDB，例如
spring application including the code
Spring 的应用程序，包括代码
rate dependency in the project with God
与上帝对项目的依赖性
will come up the entities automatically
将自动出现实体
and we have dynamic finders criteria
我们有动态的发现者条件
specialist and methods validations are
专家和方法验证是
not and we don't need implements getters
不需要，我们不需要实现获取器
and setters we have a implicit
和二传手，我们有一个隐含的
constructors implicit primary key and
构造函数隐式主键和
with this filter our code is is even
使用此过滤器，我们的代码是均匀的
even simple only the problem is I don't
甚至简单，唯一的问题是我没有
know if this is being supported yet okay
知道这是否受到支持，还可以
but I go to show you an example because
但是我去给你看一个例子，因为
I think is interested this is customer
我认为有兴趣这是客户
domain class with God I I change the
域类与神二世改变了
dependency of Java persistence for
Java持久性的依赖关系
Grails
ils子
persistent this is sorry this is the day
坚持这很抱歉这是今天
class with with groovy and missing gold
带有时髦和缺少金的类
okay now see how to use Alamein class
好，现在看看如何使用Alamein类
with dorm for example we can instance a
以宿舍为例，我们可以实例化一个
new object of the class with a map in
带有地图的类的新对象
the constructor and we have now defined
构造函数，我们现在定义了
this constructor and Nottingham we have
这个构造函数和诺丁汉，我们有
dynamic finders without implemented for
没有实现的动态查找器
example final-final by some attribute
某些属性的示例最终决赛
get many more criterias and so on and
得到更多的标准等等
these these are the dependencies that
这些是这些
you can you have to include in your in
您可以将其包含在
your Gradle that will fight to use to
您的Gradle会用来战斗
use world with even Nate and I go to
与内特一起使用世界，我去
show you the example
给你看例子
in the middle
在中间
we have never been there
我们从未去过那里
and we danced late
我们跳舞晚了
great girl even Nate Springwood okay
伟大的女孩，甚至内特·斯普林伍德都可以
also only I think the customer entity in
也只有我认为
this case the employees grades that
在这种情况下，员工对
persistence in the application main
在应用程序中的持久性
class attained the way to create new
全班学习了创造新事物的方法
customers find the custom made with
客户找到与
metal placed me get my my last by last
金属让我得到了我的最后一刻
name okay and now we go to run
好的，现在我们开始运行
this is very difficult with small mirror
用小镜子很难做到
this place
这个地方
and you can see now we have not a
您现在可以看到我们还没有
customer repository because we we are
客户资源库，因为我们
using a girl and we need to use the
使用一个女孩，我们需要使用
repository as in the case of spring that
像 Spring 一样
JPA we go to see the example
JPA我们去看看例子
um this is the same okay no no change
嗯，这是一样的，好的，没有变化
the last is something where you can use
最后是可以使用的东西
groovy and in this case a component of
groovy，在这种情况下是
Graves is a DSPs as gone since Grails to
Graves是从Grails到
that fall we can use these piece do we
那年秋天，我们可以使用这些作品吗
serve webpages outside of great but in
在很棒的网站之外提供网页
the same case of gone I'm not really
同样的情况，我不是真的
sure if currently it is supported but I
确定当前是否支持，但是我
go to to show you the example weakest
去给你展示最弱的例子
piece we have a large list of packed
件，我们有很多包装
libraries now that we can use to make
现在可以用来制作图书馆
our views more simple also we can create
我们的观点更简单，我们也可以创建
easily our own tags or we can define
轻松地我们自己的标签，或者我们可以定义
logout templates and reuse the code
注销模板并重用代码
easily this is these are some some piece
容易地，这是一些东西
of code of how to use from some tags of
的一些标签中如何使用的代码集
years piece for example conditional tabs
年件，例如条件标签
if and yet it writes all do it or using
如果并且仍然将其全部写入或使用
a finder that iteration is with a
一个迭代器与
condition for example here also the use
条件例如在这里也使用
of G date format to render template
日期格式的渲染模板
sending a model many more many more
发送模型更多
talks i also remind that you can you can
会谈我也提醒您可以
implement your contacts easily with
轻松实现您的联系人
video space they dependency that you
他们依赖的视频空间
need to include are these
这些需要包括
and I'll get to two to complete this
我将完成两个任务
talk I want to tell my conclusion of all
谈话我想告诉我所有结论
this why use glue in if you use grooving
这就是为什么在使用开槽时要使用胶水的原因
as I've said before your application has
正如我之前所说的
less lines of code so less errors and if
更少的代码行，因此更少的错误，如果
there are less errors you can find them
您可以找到的错误更少
easily so you will be more productive
轻松地进行，因此您将更有生产力
remember with groovy you can get more
记住groovy可以获得更多
more features for your project and you
您项目的更多功能以及您
can implement cool tests and you can use
可以执行很酷的测试，您可以使用
cool utilities and so this is a you have
很酷的实用程序，所以这是您拥有的
for me
为了我
super Beta mean I sit through it and
超级Beta版意味着我可以通过它
then why not use glue into the stream
那为什么不使用胶水
both applications use groovy try to
两个应用程序都使用groovy尝试
introduce be tweet in the application
在应用程序中引入推特
for example begin with a spoke test
例如以口语测试开始
later introduced groove in the code of
后来在代码中介绍了凹槽
your services for example and so on I
例如您的服务等等
finished I have finish it before they
在他们之前我已经完成了
they time before their 4 o clock but
他们在凌晨4点钟前计时，但
that's all thank you
那就谢谢你了